A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Administrative Files, RG 1 FA427
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administrative, 1952, 1954-2006; 1; 108.25 Cubic Feet 246 document boxes.
  - ACC records of the JDR 3rd Fund, 1952, 1954-1955, 1957-1989; 1
    - Director's Office, 1955, 1957-1989; 3
      - U. S. Individuals, 1958, 1960-1980, 1983-1984, 1989; 19
        - C, 1964, 1964-1980, 1984
          - Conway, Constance Bond, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 2098)
          - Cook, Kay, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 2099)
          - Coombs, Orde, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 2100)
          - Cooper, Bernarr, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 2101)
          - Cooper, John C., 1966-1969, 1971, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 2102)
          - Copeland, Rebecca L., 1978 (Box 73, Folder 2103)
          - Copland, Aaron, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 2104)
          - Coreil, Clyde, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 2105)
          - Corey, Thomas C., 1979 (Box 73, Folder 2106)
          - Corman, Cid, 1965-1966, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 2107)
          - Coveney, Richard J., 1970 (Box 73, Folder 2108)
          - Cowen, John E., 1980 (Box 73, Folder 2109)
          - Cox, Sally, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 2110)
          - Cox, Susan, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 2111)
          - Craig, Dale A., 1975 (Box 73, Folder 2112)
          - Crockett, Barbara, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 2113)
          - Croizier, Ralph C., 1972 (Box 73, Folder 2114)
          - Crystal, Eric, 1971-1973 (Box 73, Folder 2115)
          - Csede (Csete), Paul, 1971-1972 (Box 73, Folder 2116)
          - Cueni, M., 1979 (Box 73, Folder 2117)
          - Cummings, Linda, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 2118)
          - Cunningham, Merce, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 2119)
          - Curchack, Fred I., 1974, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 2120)
          - Curry, Daniel F., 1978 (Box 73, Folder 2121)
          - Curtiss, Marie Joy, 1971, 1974, 1976-1978 (Box 73, Folder 2122)
          - Custead, H. J., Jr., 1976 (Box 73, Folder 2123)
          - Czarnecki, Joseph P., 1977 (Box 73, Folder 2124)
          - Czarra, Penelope Lane, 1975-1976 (Box 73, Folder 2125)
        - D, 1965-1966, 1968-1980, 1989
          - Dalton, Bonnie, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 2126)
          - Daly, Joseph, 1978-1979 (Box 73, Folder 2127)
          - Danowski, Helen K., 1980 (Box 73, Folder 2128)
          - Dash, Ratilekha, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 2129)
          - Davenport, Thomas, 1972, 1974-1975 (Box 73, Folder 2130)
          - Davidson, J. LeRoy, 1965, 1969, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 2131)
          - Davidson, Marilyn, 1975-1976 (Box 73, Folder 2132)
          - Davies, Hugh S., 1970 (Box 73, Folder 2133)
          - Davis, Lynn, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 2134)
          - Davis, P. Douglas, 1973, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 2135)
          - Davis, Sydney, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 2136)
          - Davison, Peter, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 2137)
          - Dawkins, David, 1971, 1973, 1975-1976, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 2138)
          - De Blasio, Anthony, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 2139)
          - de Boer, Frederik, 1973-1974 (Box 73, Folder 2140)
          - Debold, Robert E., 1969-1970 (Box 73, Folder 2141)
          - DeCola, Frank, 1969-1971 (Box 73, Folder 2142)
          - Del Valle, Joseph B., 1969, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 2143)
          - Delli, Bertrun, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 2144)
          - DeMarco, Anthony F., 1977 (Box 74, Folder 2145)
          - de Menil, Jean (John) & Dominique, 1966, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 2146)
          - de Montaudouin, Maya, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 2147)
          - de Peaux, Richard, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 2148)
          - De Reeves, Maria C., 1950, 1973-1974 (Box 74, Folder 2149)
          - DeRicco, Hank, 1976 (Box 74, Folder 2150)
          - Deschamps, Francois, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 2151)
          - Descutner, Janet, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 2152)
          - Detwiler, Joseph, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 2153)
          - DeWitt, Anne, 1978 (Box 74, Folder 2154)
          - d'Harnoncourt, Anne, 1969, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 2154B)
          - Dickinson, Storm, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 2155)
          - Diffloth, Danielle G., 1969-1970 (Box 74, Folder 2156)
          - Diksheet, Snehal, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 2157)
          - Dingman, Jill, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 2158)
          - Dirks, Jewel, 1978 (Box 74, Folder 2159)
          - di San Miniato, Duke Arturo Pini, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 2160)
          - Dishinger, R. Christian, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 2161)
          - Dittrich, Kathinka, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 2162)
          - Dixon, Angie, 1978 (Box 74, Folder 2163)
          - Dobbins, K. Walton, 1976 (Box 74, Folder 2164)
          - Dobi, Steve, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 2165)
          - Dodge, Charles, 1970, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 2166)
          - Dolan, Patricia, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 2167)
          - Dolejs, Charles, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 2168)
          - Don-Pedro, George, 1978-1979 (Box 74, Folder 2169)
          - Dooley, Pat, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 2170)
          - Dorff, Linda L., 1976 (Box 74, Folder 2171)
          - Dorra, Henri, 1965 (Box 74, Folder 2172)
          - Dourmashkin, Barbara, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 2173)
          - Downs, Hugh R., 1979 (Box 74, Folder 2174)
          - Downs, Ray C., 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder 2175)
          - Doyle, William S., 1976 (Box 74, Folder 2176)
          - Dragol, Marc, 1969, 1974-1975 (Box 74, Folder 2177)
          - Drobny, Edwin, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 2178)
          - Drucker, Charles, 1977-1978 (Box 74, Folder 2179)
          - Drury, Jonathan, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 2180)
          - Drutman, Irving, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 2181)
          - Dube, Eleanor J., 1971 (Box 74, Folder 2182)
          - Dubow, Neville (Box 74, Folder 2183)
          - Dugan, W. O., 1977 (Box 74, Folder 2184)
          - Duggar, Margaret, 1974-1975 (Box 74, Folder 2185)
          - Dugger, John, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 2186)
          - Dumo, Shirley A., 1979 (Box 74, Folder 2187)
          - Duncavage, Marybeth A., 1976 (Box 74, Folder 2188)
          - Dundon, Janice, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 2189)
          - Dunlap, Monica, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 2190)
          - Dupree, Nancy H., 1975, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 2191)
          - Durfee, Susan, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 2192)
          - Dyer, Ann, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 2193)
        - E, 1958, 1965-1966, 1968-1978
          - Eames, Charles, 1958, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 2194)
          - Easton, Walter, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 2195)
          - Edwards, Tacy G., 1978 (Box 74, Folder 2196)
          - Eichenberg, Fritz, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 2197)
          - Eide, Elling O., 1965-1966, 1976 (Box 74, Folder 2198)
          - Eke, Verno Munro, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 2199)
          - Elder, Shonti, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 2200)
          - Elliott, Roger A., 1968 (Box 74, Folder 2201)
          - Elson, Charles, 1968-1969 (Box 74, Folder 2202)
          - Emmett, Arielle, 1976 (Box 74, Folder 2203)
          - Emmons, Zette, 1975, 1978 (Box 74, Folder 2204)
          - Enkoji, Ann O., 1971 (Box 74, Folder 2205)
          - Erda, Bettie, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder 2206)
          - Erlanger, Margaret, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 2207)
          - Erskine, Maren, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 2208)
          - Ervin, Charles Wesley, 1971, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 2209)
          - Espina, A. Beaunoni, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 2210)
          - Estabrook, Penelope, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 2211)
          - Ettinghausen, Richard, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 2212)
          - Eurich, Alice A., 1964, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 2212B)
          - Evans, Richard, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 2213)
          - Evenson, Marianne, 1978 (Box 74, Folder 2214)
        - F, 1966-1980
          - Faegre, Aron, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 2215)
          - Fagan, Joel L., 1975 (Box 74, Folder 2216)
          - Fahy, Mimi, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 2217)
          - Fairman, Huck, 1976 (Box 74, Folder 2218)
          - Falkenhainer, Carl W., 1973 (Box 74, Folder 2219)
          - Faris, Richard L., 1979 (Box 74, Folder 2220)
          - Farrelly, David, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 2221)
          - Farris, Colleen M., 1976 (Box 75, Folder 2222)
          - Feinman, Lynne, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 2223)
          - Feldman, Jerome, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 2224)
          - Ferretti, John, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 2225)
          - Feulner, Cliff, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 2226)
          - Fidoten, Douglas C., 1975 (Box 75, Folder 2227)
          - Fiedler, Patricia A., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 2228)
          - Field, Kathryn, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 2229)
          - Findly, Ellison Banks, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 2230)
          - Finkelstein, Robert A., 1975 (Box 75, Folder 2231)
          - Finkelstein, Stuart, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 2232)
          - Fischel, Andrea, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 2233)
          - Fischer, George, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 2234)
          - Fisher, Lue Ann, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 2235)
          - Fischer, Michael A., 1976 (Box 75, Folder 2236)
          - Fitch, Joseph C., 1967 (Box 75, Folder 2237)
          - Fitzgerald, Patrice M., 1978 (Box 75, Folder 2238)
          - Fix, Dorothy, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 2239)
          - Flagg, Charles, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 2240)
          - Flaherty, Charles F., 1975-1976 (Box 75, Folder 2241)
          - Flam, Louis, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 2242)
          - Fleisher, Robert, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 2243)
          - Fleming, Robert, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 2244)
          - Flittie, Jacqueline, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 2245)
          - Fonoroff, Paul, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 2246)
          - Ford, Jane, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 2247)
          - Ford, John Gilmore, 1974, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 2248)
          - Foresta, Don, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 2249)
          - Foster, Gretchen, 1980 (Box 75, Folder 2250)
          - Fourcade, Xavier, 1957, 1966, 1968-1970 (Box 75, Folder 2251)
          - Francis, Peter, Jr., 1979 (Box 75, Folder 2252)
          - Franson, Sonya, 1972 (Box 75, Folder 2253)
          - Fredericks, Claude, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 2254)
          - Fredriksen, John C., 1980 (Box 75, Folder 2255)
          - Freeman, Michael, 1970-1971 (Box 75, Folder 2256)
          - Frenkel, Michael, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 2257)
          - Friedmann, Arnold, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 2258)
          - Frye, Stanley, 1975-1976 (Box 75, Folder 2259)
          - Funt, David P., 1980 (Box 75, Folder 2260)
          - Furgiuele, Harriet R., 1975 (Box 75, Folder 2261)
        - G, 1963-1968, 1970-1980
          - Gartel, Laurence M., 1978 (Box 75, Folder 2262)
          - Garvin, Philip R., 1970 (Box 75, Folder 2263)
          - Garza, Michele, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 2264)
          - Garzio, Angelo C., 1972 (Box 75, Folder 2265)
          - Gavert, Olive, 1965 (Box 75, Folder 2266)
          - Gearhart, Rena, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 2267)
          - Gelman, Anita, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 2268)
          - Gershowitz, Karen, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 2269)
          - Gershumy-Segura, Phyllis, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 2270)
          - Gianno, Rosemary, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 2271)
          - Gilbert, Sally, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 2272)
          - Giles, Francis, 1975, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 2273)
          - Gilfillan, Edward S., 1972-1973 (Box 75, Folder 2274)
          - Gillespie, Gregory, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 2275)
          - Gjermundson, Kristi Jo, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 2276)
          - Glabman, Tom, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 2277)
          - Glade, Margaret R., 1977 (Box 75, Folder 2278)
          - Glassman, Helen, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 2279)
          - Glewwe, Lois, 1974-1975 (Box 75, Folder 2280)
          - Glimcher, Summer, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 2281)
          - Glomb, Wendy, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 2282)
          - Gluck, Peter L., 1971-1972 (Box 75, Folder 2283)
          - Glum, Peter, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 2284)
          - Godsman, Jean, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 2285)
          - Goelet, John, 1966-1967 (Box 75, Folder 2286)
          - Gokey, Margaret A., 1975, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 2287)
          - Goldberg, Joshua, 1972 (Box 75, Folder 2288)
          - Goldblatt, Elizabeth, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 2289)
          - Goldman, Debra, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 2290)
          - Goldstein, Martha, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 2291)
          - Goldstein, Mel, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 2292)
          - Goldwater, Robert, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 2293)
          - Gomez, Vincent E., 1979 (Box 75, Folder 2294)
          - Gonzaga, Otoniel Eduardo, 1970-1972 (Box 75, Folder 2295)
          - Goodberg, Robert, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 2296)
          - Gorman, Chester F., 1976 (Box 75, Folder 2297)
          - Gorn, Steven T., 1974 (Box 75, Folder 2298)
          - Gorski, Dan, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 2299)
          - Gorsline, Douglas Warner, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 2300)
          - Gotcher, Vicki, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 2301)
          - Goto, Pamela J., 1975 (Box 76, Folder 2302)
          - Gottlieb, Adolph, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 2303)
          - Grad, Barbara, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 2304)
          - Graf, Howard, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 2306)
          - Graff, Robert, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 2307)
          - Gramberg, Liliana, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 2308)
          - Graves, Bradford, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 2309)
          - Grebanier, Joseph P., 1971 (Box 76, Folder 2310)
          - Greenberg, Clement, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 2311)
          - Greene, Alexis, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 2312)
          - Greenman, John Francis, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 2313)
          - Greenway, Sadie, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 2314)
          - Griese, Carolyn, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 2315)
          - Griffing, Robert P., Jr., 1966, 1973, 1980 (Box 76, Folder 2316)
          - Grilli, Peter M., 1968 (Box 76, Folder 2317)
          - Grimson, S. B., 1974 (Box 76, Folder 2318)
          - Gronvold, Janice, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 2319)
          - Gross, Richard, 1980 (Box 76, Folder 2320)
          - Gunderson, Warren M., 1974 (Box 76, Folder 2321)
          - Guidote, Cecile, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 2322)
          - Gumbiner, Richard A., 1975 (Box 76, Folder 2323)
          - Gunther, John, 1967 (Box 76, Folder 2324)
          - Gustafson, Frederic R., 1966 (Box 76, Folder 2325)
          - Gussow, Alan, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 2326)
          - Gutheim, Frederick, 1963-1964, 1967, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 2327)
          - Gutkind, Gabriele, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 2328)
          - Guyer, David L., 1971 (Box 76, Folder 2329)
        - H, 1961-1962, 1964, 1966-1978, 1980
          - Haar, Francis, 1968-1969 (Box 76, Folder 2330)
          - Haas, Ken, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 2331)
          - Haas, Steven, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 2332)
          - Haddad, Sam, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 2333)
          - Hahn, Gerald, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 2334)
          - Haight, Giuliana, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 2335)
          - Hale, Mary, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 2336)
          - Hall, Kenneth R., 1974 (Box 76, Folder 2337)
          - Hall, Melanie, 1976-1977 (Box 76, Folder 2338)
          - Hall, Norman V., 1971 (Box 76, Folder 2339)
          - Hallet, Stanley, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 2340)
          - Halsall, Tom, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 2341)
          - Hambly, Deborah, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 2342)
          - Hamidi, Sadeghh, 1980 (Box 76, Folder 2343)
          - Hamilton, Ishvani, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 2344)
          - Hamilton, Uve, 1973-1974 (Box 76, Folder 2345)
          - Hammond, Herbert, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 2346)
          - Hancock, William, 1971, 1976-1977 (Box 76, Folder 2347)
          - Hanish, Babette S., 1970-1974 (Box 76, Folder 2348)
          - Hanks, Lucien M., 1976 (Box 76, Folder 2349)
          - Hannemann, Yvonne, 1972, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 2350)
          - Hansen, Kathryn G., 1969-1971, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 2351)
          - Hardesty, James M., 1979 (Box 76, Folder 2352)
          - Harding, Beatrice L., 1972 (Box 76, Folder 2353)
          - Hare, David & Denise, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 2354)
          - Harnden, Peter, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 2355)
          - Harris, E. John, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 2356)
          - Harter, Mark M., 1971 (Box 76, Folder 2357)
          - Harter, Patricia M., 1978 (Box 76, Folder 2358)
          - Hartman, Roger, 1973-1974 (Box 76, Folder 2359)
          - Haskins, John F., 1975-1976 (Box 77, Folder 2360)
          - Haslam, Herbert, 1969 (Box 77, Folder 2361)
          - Hatch, James V., 1968-1969 (Box 77, Folder 2362)
          - Hatt, Robert T., 1966-1968 (Box 77, Folder 2363)
          - Hawkins, Everett D., 1970 (Box 77, Folder 2364)
          - Hawkins, Richard S. D., 1967, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 2365)
          - Hawkins, Rodger, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 2366)
          - Hedges, Inez, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 2367)
          - Heeramaneck, Nasli M., 1971 (Box 77, Folder 2368)
          - Hehmeyer, Alexander, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 2369)
          - Heiter, Jack, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 2370)
          - Held, David, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 2371)
          - Helstein, Melvyn, 1968, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 2372)
          - Helweg, Arthur W., 1969 (Box 77, Folder 2373)
          - Henrie, Edwin J., 1975 (Box 77, Folder 2374)
          - Henry, Marcia, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 2375)
          - Henry, Margaret, 1967 (Box 77, Folder 2376)
          - Herman, Dean A., 1970 (Box 77, Folder 2377)
          - Herr, Laurin, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 2378)
          - Herwitz, Chester E., 1974 (Box 77, Folder 2379)
          - Hess, Linda, 1977-1978 (Box 77, Folder 2380)
          - Hess, Thomas B., 1968 (Box 77, Folder 2381)
          - Heston, Mary Beth, 1978-1979 (Box 77, Folder 2382)
          - Higbie, Sandra, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 2383)
          - Higgins, Chester A., Jr., 1971, 1974-1977 (Box 77, Folder 2384)
          - Hightower, John B., 1969 (Box 77, Folder 2385)
          - Hillman, Elston, 1969 (Box 77, Folder 2387)
          - Hillyer, Kazuko, 1969, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 2388)
          - Hirsch, Jim, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 2389)
          - Hitchens, Gordon, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 2390)
          - Hobbs, ,John K., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 2391)
          - Hock, Robert D., 1971 (Box 77, Folder 2392)
          - Hodson, Lynn, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 2393)
          - Hoffer, Phil, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 2394)
          - Hoffman, Michael E., 1976-1977 (Box 77, Folder 2395)
          - Hoffman, Stanley Brian, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 2396)
          - Hofmann, Hans, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 2397)
          - Hokenson, Jan, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 2398)
          - Holden, Philip N., 1975 (Box 77, Folder 2399)
          - Hollenbeck, Philip, 1972, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 2400)
          - Holm, David L., 1972 (Box 77, Folder 2401)
          - Holmes, Iwan W. A. S., 1971 (Box 77, Folder 2402)
          - Hom, Sam B., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 2403)
          - Homans, Robert, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 2404)
          - Hoo, Joel, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 2405)
          - Hooper, Keith A., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 2406)
          - Hopper, William H., 1974 (Box 77, Folder 2407)
          - Horii, Gertrude, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 2408)
          - Horn, Axel, 1965 (Box 77, Folder 2409)
          - Horowitz, Beth, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 2410)
          - Hoshijo, Kathy, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 2411)
          - Hosken, Fran P., 1968-1975 (Box 77, Folder 2412)
          - Houghton, Norris, 1967-1968, 1971-1972 (Box 77, Folder 2412B)
          - Howard, Mel, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 2413)
          - Hsu, Fu Chuan, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 2414)
          - Hsu, Joan, Overseas Chinese Music & Arts Center, Inc., 1961-1962, 1964, 1970, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2415)
          - Hsu, Raymond, 1973-1974, 1976-1979 (Box 78, Folder 2416)
          - Hsu, Samuel, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 2417)
          - Hu, William C., 1972 (Box 78, Folder 2418)
          - Huber, Louisa G. Fitzgerald, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 2419)
          - Hudson, Ben, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 2420)
          - Hughes, David H., 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2421)
          - Hughes, Sukey, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 2422)
          - Hull, Louisa, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 2423)
          - Hunter, Daniel H., Jr, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 2424)
          - Hunter, Thomas M., 1977 (Box 78, Folder 2425)
          - Huntington, John C., 1975 (Box 78, Folder 2426)
          - Huntington, Susan, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 2427)
          - Hurrie, Harriotte, 1976, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 2428)
          - Hurwich, Cecelia, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 2429)
          - Hutchins, Francis G., 1976-1977 (Box 78, Folder 2430)
          - Hutto, Ralph, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 2431)
        - I, 1963-1964, 1971, 1974-1978
          - Ieronimo, Giuliano C., 1978 (Box 78, Folder 2432)
          - Imbs, Thomas Justin, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 2433)
          - Irons, Allan W., 1971 (Box 78, Folder 2434)
          - Irons, David, 1974-1975 (Box 78, Folder 2435)
          - Irwin, Marion, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 2436)
          - Iscan, Walda E., 1976 (Box 78, Folder 2437)
          - Isenberg, Artur, 1963-1964 (Box 78, Folder 2438)
        - J, 1965, 1968-1980
          - Jackson, Dan, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 2440)
          - Jackson, Gary B., 1971 (Box 78, Folder 2441)
          - Jacobs, Dorothy, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 2442)
          - Jacobs, Garry, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 2443)
          - Jacobson, Adele, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 2444)
          - Jaffe, Harold, 1970 (Box 78, Folder 2445)
          - Jafree, I. (Box 78, Folder 2446)
          - Jahnke, Roger DeMar, 1971, 1973-1975 (Box 78, Folder 2447)
          - Jahoda, Fritz, 1970-1971 (Box 78, Folder 2448)
          - Jameson, Philip, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 2449)
          - Jennings, Barbara, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 2450)
          - Jennings, Mildred, 1970 (Box 78, Folder 2451)
          - Jervis, Nancy, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 2452)
          - Jew, Miller, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 2453)
          - Jochnowitz, Johann Michael, 1970 (Box 78, Folder 2454)
          - Johnson, Benedicte Grima, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 2455)
          - Johnson, David Hoyt, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 2456)
          - Johnson, Nancy C., 1975 (Box 78, Folder 2457)
          - Johnson, Philip, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 2458)
          - Jolly-Gates, Karen, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 2459)
          - Jones, Betty, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 2460)
          - Jones, Clifford Reis & Jones, Betty True, 1968-1969, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 2461)
          - Jones, Cranston, 1968 (Box 78, Folder 2462)
          - Jones, George Bobby, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 2463)
          - Jones, Jebbora, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 2464)
          - Jones, Megan Llinos, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 2465)
          - Jones, Stacey, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 2466)
          - Joseph, Bruce, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder 2467)
          - Joshua, Yoram, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 2468)
          - Jue, Gerald, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 2469)
          - Jules-Rosette, Bennetta, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 2470)
          - Julien, Daniel, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 2471)
        - K, 1964-1979
          - Kaffenberger, K. Richard, 1976 (Box 79, Folder 2472)
          - Kahn, Gail A., 1971 (Box 79, Folder 2473)
          - Kalberkamp, Michelle L. & Peter, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 2474)
          - Kale, Pramod, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 2475)
          - Kalman, Bela T., 1977 (Box 79, Folder 2476)
          - Kandell, Alice, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 2477)
          - Kang, Samuel, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 2478)
          - Kanowsky, Bernadette, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 2479)
          - Kao, Ruth Yu-Hsin, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 2480)
          - Kapadia, Sen, 1976 (Box 79, Folder 2481)
          - Kaplan, Eve, 1975 (Box 79, Folder 2482)
          - Kaplan, Philip, 1979 (Box 79, Folder 2483)
          - Kardoss, John, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 2484)
          - Kassebaum, Gene, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 2485)
          - Kato, Shioh, 1979 (Box 79, Folder 2486)
          - Kats, Ivan, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 2487)
          - Katz, Milton, 1970 (Box 79, Folder 2488)
          - Kawaguchi, Karen, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 2489)
          - Keck, Sheldon & Caroline, 1970 (Box 79, Folder 2490)
          - Kennan, George F., 1969 (Box 79, Folder 2491)
          - Kennedy, Lanie, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 2492)
          - Kennedy, Margaret F., 1971 (Box 79, Folder 2493)
          - Kerman, Freda, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 2494)
          - Kerry, Lucyann, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 2495)
          - Kessler, Marjorie, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 2496)